Guide to the Architect & Engineer Collection circa 1790-1989 PR 3
New-York Historical Society
- Unidentified Creators (80 projects)
  - 49 East 76th Street, Elevations and Floor Plans (PR 3-149) (Folder PR 3-149)
  - Hunter House (PR 3-150) (Folder PR 3-150)
  - F. Kurtz Building, 90th Street and Fifth Avenue (PR 3-151) (Folder PR 3-151)
  - Springler Institute, Front Elevation (PR 3-152) (Folder PR 3-152)
  - Park Building (PR 3-153) (Folder PR 3-153)
  - House for Dr. Robinson, Flue Section of Walls Nos. 1-6 (PR 3-154) (Folder PR 3-154)
  - House for John Rogers, Esq., Elevations and Floor Plans (PR 3-155) (Folder PR 3-155)
  - House on Grand Street, Elevations and Floor Plans (PR 3-156) (Folder PR 3-156)
  - Houses on 95th Street and 8th Avenue, Elevations and Sections (PR 3-157) (Folder PR 3-157)
  - Commercial Building on 24th Street, Elevations (PR 3-158) (Folder PR 3-158)
  - Commercial Building at Broadway and 47th Street, Elevations (PR 3-159) (Folder PR 3-159)
  - Unidentified House, Elevations (PR 3-160) (Folder PR 3-160)
  - Commercial Building on Cedar Street (PR 3-161), 1867 (Folder PR 3-161)
  - Henry C. Sturges Residence, 56 West 34th Street, Proposed Alterations (PR 3-162) (Folder PR 3-162)
  - Unidentified House, Floor Plans, Elevations, and Perspective Views (PR 3-163) (Folder PR 3-163)
  - Unidentified House, Floor Plans and Elevations (PR 3-164) (Folder PR 3-164)
  - New York Sewers, Sections and Plans (PR 3-165), 1898-1899 (Folder PR 3-165)
  - Prints of Illustrations of Fortification Plans (PR 3-166) (Folder PR 3-166)
  - Marshall O. Roberts Estate, Floor Plans, Elevations and Sections (PR 3-167) (Folder PR 3-167)
  - Commercial Building at Broadway and Fifth Avenue, Elevations (PR 3-168) (Folder PR 3-168)
  - Unidentified Public Building [Possibly Hospital or Orphanage], Elevations (PR 3-169) (Folder PR 3-169)
  - Morris-Jumel Mansion, Floor Plans (PR 3-170) (Folder PR 3-170)
  - West Side Improvement, Plans for Highway at Riverside Drive (PR 3-175), 1925-1929 (Folder PR 3-175)
  - Harlem River Bridge and Aqueduct Drawings (PR 3-176) (Folder PR 3-176)
  - Church in Massachusetts, Plans (PR 3-181), 1859 (Folder PR 3-181)
  - Water Main Section Drawing (PR 3-186) (Folder PR 3-186)
  - Washington Square Reformed Dutch Church, Alterations to Basement (PR 3-187), 1866 (Folder PR 3-187)
  - Peter Hetzog Theological Hall, Floor Plans, (PR 3-188), 1876 (Folder PR 3-188)
  - Unidentified Floor Plan (PR 3-189) (Folder PR 3-189)
  - New York Tunnels and Aqueduct, Excavation Drawings (PR 3-190) (Folder PR 3-190)
  - Cour de Bergeries (PR 3-192) (Folder PR 3-192)
  - Various Unidentified Churches, Elevations, Sections, and Floor Plans (PR 3-197) (Folder PR 3-197)
  - Village of Larchmont Sewer Plans (PR 3-199), 1899 (Folder PR 3-199)
  - Unidentified Roof Framing Plans (PR 3-200) (Folder PR 3-200)
  - Unidentified Building, Elevation and Plan (PR 3-201) (Folder PR 3-201)
  - Abercrombie and Fitch, Floor Plans (PR 3-203) (Folder PR 3-203)
  - Plans for Piers on River Front, 151 Street to 158 Street (PR 3-211) (Folder PR 3-211)
  - Gracie Mansion, Front Elevation (PR 3-220) (Folder PR 3-220)
  - 25 Sutton Place, Floor Plans (PR 3-227) (Folder PR 3-227)
  - Bank Street Row House, Floor Plan (PR 3-229) (Folder PR 3-229)
  - President's Square, Connecting Building Between War and Navy Offices (PR 3-231) (Folder PR 3-231)